https://www.wiringproducts.com/privacy-policy

Phone:800-549-0243
HomeAll CategoriesCustom ProductsCustom Rocker SwitchesCustom Switch PanelsCustom Circuit Breaker PanelsCustom Indicator PanelsCustom Fuse Panels
Customer Service
Order StatusTerms & ConditionsContact UsTech Support ArticlesPrivacy PolicyFAQAccountAbout UsCart
Last updated: June 27, 2018
This page informs you of WiringProducts, Ltd. policies involving the collection and use of Personal Information we receive from website visitors and customers.We use your information only for providing products and services directly related to business transactions on our site. By using our site, you agree to the collection and use of certain information in accordance with this policy.
Information We Collect And Use - Visitors to our web site:
Log Data - We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, web browser type, web browser version, the different pages that you visit on our web site, the time and date of your visit, and other statistics.  In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze visitors to our site.
Cookies -  Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer.  Like many web sites, we use "cookies" to collect information such as items added to your shopping cart. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use our website to make an online purchase.
Information We Collect And Use - Customers and Subscribers:
Order Information - We collect certain information necessary in the normal course of business to verify your purchase and to provide the goods and services purchased from our website.  This includes your name, address, phone number, and email address.  We may use your phone number and email address to contact you about your order, and we may use your email to occasionally send you new product information or promotional material.  You can remove your email from our system by simply clicking on the unsubscribe link found on these emails, and you will no longer receive them.
Security - The security of your Personal Information is important to us.  We utilize the latest SSL encryption across our website provided by Comodo.  Unfortunately, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy Policy - This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 27, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.  If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
All CategoriesAutomotive Wire and Cable Battery and Power Distribution Cable Ties and Clamps Circuit Breakers - Automotive Connectors and Wire Terminals Custom Electrical Products Electrical Kits Fuses, Fuse Blocks and Fuse Holders Heat Shrink Tubing Lights - 12 Volt Switches, Relays, & Flashers Tapes, Grommets, and Chemicals Tools Wire Loom Sales and Close Outs
Other products you may be interested in
#10 Stud 8 AWG Heavy Duty Vinyl Ring Terminal 5 Pieces
5 Piece economy package. Heavy duty 8 gauge vinyl insulated ring terminal. #10 Stud size. Tin...
Part #: WT-454105
Quantity
Price ea.
1 + $4.78
$4.78
10 Amp Bussmann ATC Circuit Breaker Auto Reset
Bussmann ATC thermal Circuit Breaker - Auto Reset - 10 Amp - Type 1 auto reset circuit breakers...
Part #: CB-ATC1-10
Quantity
Price ea.
1 + $7.70 5 + $6.54 25 + $5.39
$7.70
Toggle Switch - 20 Amp Screw Terminal - DPDT ON-OFF-ON
Toggle Switch - 20 Amp Screw Terminal - DPDT ON-OFF-ON
High power toggle switches can be used for...
Part #: TS-DPDT-ONOFFON-SMT
Quantity
Price ea.
1 + $12.78 5 + $10.86 25 + $8.95
$12.78
Stud Junction Block - 8 Stud
Stud Junction Block - 8 Stud - Isolated stud-type terminal block is rated at 30 amps per stud -...
Part #: WT-8SJB
Quantity
Price ea.
1 + $15.79
$15.79
#6 Stud Non-Insulated Spade Terminals 16-14 Gauge 100 Pieces
16-14 AWG Uninsulated spade/fork terminals. #6 fork size. Made from tin plated copper. Temperature...
Part #: WT-USB06
Quantity
Price ea.
1 + $7.27
$7.27
1,000ft. Spool Red 20 gauge Primary Automotive Wire
20 gauge Primary Automotive Wire - Red
- 1,000 Ft. Spool. Copper core made up of 10 strands of 30...
Part #: W-20P-RE
Quantity
Price ea.
1 + $95.21
$95.21
3/0 Gauge Black Battery Cable - By the Foot
3/0 Gauge (AWG) black battery cable has an amperage capacity of 300 amps at 12 volts DC and a...
Part #: W-BCB-3/0
Length(ft.)
Price per ft.
1 + $9.74 5 + $8.74 25 + $7.73 100 + $6.72
$9.74
14 gauge Red SXL Automotive Wire 15 Ft. Package
25ft. Increments of 14 Gauge Red Cross-linked Automotive Wire. Suitable for engine compartment...
Part #: SBX-14RE
Quantity
Price ea.
1 + $9.87
$9.87
131 Piece Terminal Kit - No crimping tool
131 Piece Terminal Kit - No crimping tool - These kits contain a balanced stock of our most popular...
Part #: KIT-TERM-NO-TOOL
Quantity
Price ea.
1 + $30.24
$30.24
16 Gauge Black 1015 MTW Hookup Wire 500ft. Spool
500ft. Spool of 16 Gauge Black 1015 MTW Hookup Wire. Multifunctional 16 gauge wire for use in RV,...
Part #: W-16R-BK
Quantity
Price ea.
1 + $101.03
$101.03
4 Contact Flat Female Molded Connector 48'' wires
4-Contact Flat Molded Connector - Female - 48'' wire length manufactured with 16 gauge primary...
Part #: MC-4F-FLAT-48L
Quantity
Price ea.
1 + $6.17
$6.17
6 Gauge Green THHN Stranded Wire 10ft. Length
6 AWG Green THHN Wire in a 10ft. Length. Multiple lengths will be continuous unless specified...
Part #: W-06THHNSTR-GR
Quantity
Price ea.
Bussman Short Stop Trip and Hold Circuit Breakers 12 Volt Type 2
Quick Slide Connectors (T-Tap)
HomeAll CategoriesCustom ProductsCustom Rocker SwitchesCustom Switch PanelsCustom Circuit Breaker PanelsCustom Indicator PanelsCustom Fuse Panels
Customer Service
Order StatusTerms & ConditionsContact UsTech Support ArticlesPrivacy PolicyFAQAccountAbout UsCart
